<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Ruzane</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/art.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2013-08-20T06:19:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>Holo color palette</title><link href="/blog/holo-color-palette.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2013-08-20T06:19:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Alireza Kashani</name></author><id>tag:,2013-08-20:blog/holo-color-palette.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite being slightly colorblind, I’m one of those
people who is bizarrely anal-retentive when it comes to color-schemes in
the software that I use. I use custom CSS extensions in Chrome to make
the color schemes of websites like Wikipedia, Youtube, etc a bit more
pleasing. I did some digging in the accessibility preference pane of
Adobe Reader to make the default document background a nice book-like
sepia tone which makes reading PDFs online a much less straining
endeavor (incidentally - Google Play Books &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; has a white background
which is why I greatly prefer the Amazon Kindle web app). I’ve spent
wayy too long (as I think many geeks do), customizing my terminal and
custom android ROM themes. I think you get the picture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An inadvertent data poem by &lt;a href="http://www.usfca.edu/facultydetails.aspx?id=6442485442"&gt;Dr. Cindi Thompson&lt;/a&gt;
Some playing around in Xmind (a free, open source mind-mapping software package), here is a side-by-side comparison of 1) the freesurfer workflow as it stands, 2) the workflow as it would be experienced by a user of this parallel-distribution crowdsourcing- with the web platform as a black box, and 3) a slightly more detailed picture of what would be happening with the data. &lt;img alt="Image processing pipeline comparison" src="/images/flowchart.jpg" style="width: 500px; height: auto; max-width: 100%;"/&gt;
Xmind can be downloaded for free at &lt;a href="http://xmind.net"&gt;xmind.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</summary><category term="color"></category><category term="holo"></category><category term="solarized"></category></entry></feed>